adfromhomes.com 2014-05-29

# Our Privacy Policy - Adfromhomes.com

Under what name will my purchase be charged on the credit card statement?

Your purchase will be charged under Saroj Ad Creators India Pvt. Ltd

Who can advertise through Sarojads.com?

  * To be able to shop at Sarojads.com, you should be above 18 years of age and legally allowed, by the laws governing your land, to advertise in India.
  * You need to have a valid credit card or debit card (VISA, MASTERCARD or American Express) or have a netbanking account with one of the banks enabled on our payment gateway.

I am concerned about the privacy of my personal information I have shared with Sarojads.

We understand that you value your privacy, and we respect it. Snapdeal is committed to maintaining complete confidentiality and privacy of the data that you share with us. You may go through our privacy policy. We are committed to protect your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully.

Is it safe to Login at Sarojads.com through my Facebook ID or Google ID?

Yes, it's absolutely safe to login at Sarojads through your Facebook or Google ID. We will not store your passwords in any case. 

Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:  

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at office@sarojads.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties that we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

Why do you collect the information from us?

We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and secondly, to provide you with the best possible service.

What information do you collect from us?

The type of information we will collect about you includes:

Your Name  
Address  
Phone Number  
Email Address

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.
